原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     一只虾   吃冰棒   小酸奶
翻译     詹木头   TheWalkingNerd
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     啾啾啾   吃土少女
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
双峰
第三季  第十一集
很好
Nice.
差一点
Oh, almost.
去捡
Go get it.
扔过来
Throw it in.
漂亮
Nice.
没事  我来捡
It's okay. I got it.
那边有人
There's someone there.
去告诉妈妈
Go tell Mom.
什么
What?
在哪
Where?
什么
What?
该死  我他妈没有车
Damn it! I don't have a fucking car!
贝基
Hey, Becky.
妈  我要用你的车  史蒂文出事了
Mom, I need your car. It's Steven!
亲爱的  怎么了
Honey, what's wrong?
史蒂文出事了  拜托  我要用你的车
It's Steven! Please, I need your car!
求你了  快点
Please, hurry!
好吗  快点
Okay? Hurry!
我马上过来
I'm coming right over.
抱歉  诺玛  我得离开一下
I'm sorry, Norma. I have to go.
贝基
Becky!
贝基  贝基  怎么了
Becky! Becky, what's going on?
-我恨他  -贝基
- I hate him. - Becky!
-我恨他  -怎么了
- I hate him. - What happened?
-我恨他  -贝基
- I hate him. - Becky.
贝基
Becky.
Becky!
开门  贝基  别走
Open! Becky, don't!
贝基  停车
Becky, stop!
贝基
Becky!
贝基  贝基  不
Becky! Becky, no!
贝基  停车
Becky, stop!
雪莉
Shelly!
怎么回事
What the hell?
你没事吧  亲爱的
Are you okay, sweetheart?
你能载我去双R餐厅吗  卡尔
Can you give me a ride to the Double R, Carl?
发生什么了
What the hell happened?
贝基和史蒂文又吵架了
Becky and Steven are fighting again.
天啊
Oh, God.
我们不能再快点吗  卡尔
Can't we go any faster, Carl?
我想活着到那儿  雪莉
I want to get us there in one piece, Shelly.
卡尔
Oh, Carl.
我知道那辆拖车以前出过事
I know there's been trouble in that trailer.
我们都听见了
We've all heard it.
我很心疼你还有你的女儿  知道吗  雪莉
And I feel for you and your girl, okay, Shelly?
谢谢
Thank you.
雪莉
Shelly.
诺玛  贝基把车开走了
Norma, Becky took off.
我不知道她去哪了
I don't know where she went.
我该怎么办
What should I do?
你怎么不打给博比
Why didn't you just call Bobby?
小雪
Shell?
雪莉
Shelly!
玛吉  玛吉
Maggie? Maggie!
我是卡尔
This is Carl.
常规报告  收到
10-17, copy that.
你好  卡尔
Hello, Carl.
玛吉  我用货车载雪莉·布里格斯过来
Maggie, I got Shelly Briggs here in the truck with me.
你能帮我们接通布里格斯副警长吗
Could you patch us through to Deputy Briggs?
稍等  马上接通
Hold on, please. I'll put you through.
雪莉
Shelly.
谢谢  诺玛  我一会打给你
Thanks, Norma, I'll call you back.
雪莉
Shelly.
我是布里格斯
This is Briggs.
布里格斯副警长
Deputy Briggs.
博比  我是雪莉
Bobby, it's Shelly.
贝基把车开走了
Becky took off with the car.
谁的车
Whose car?
我的
My car.
我不知道她去哪了
I don't know where she went.
博比  她手上有枪
Bobby, she's got a gun.
天啊
Oh, God.
史蒂文
Steven!
史蒂文  我知道你在里面
Steven, I know you're in there!
该死的孬种
Fucking coward!
天
God.
去你妈的  史蒂文
Damn you, Steven!
他们走了
They've left.
他们走了  他们刚走
They left. They just left.
里面没人了
There's nobody in there!
去你妈的  史蒂文
Fuck you, Steven!
警察局
Sheriff's Department.
请告诉我你在哪  女士
What's your location, please, ma'am?
汀布莱克道1601号
Sixteen-oh-one Timberlake Drive?
已派警员前去
Someone's on the way.
警察局  你在哪里
Sheriff's Department. What's your location?
已派警员前去
Someone's on the way.
警察局  你在哪里
Sheriff's Department. What's your location?
已派警员前去
Someone's on the way.
警察局
Sheriff's Department.
请问你在哪里
What's your location, please?
已派警员前去
Someone's on the way.
625  常规报告
Six twenty-five, 10-17.
收到
Copy that.
南达科州  鹿角镇
就是这里吗
This is the place?
-塔米  -怎么了
- Tammy? - Yep?
你和黑斯廷斯一起去
You go work with Hastings.
找到他的准确位置
Find out exactly where he went.
我就不去了
This is as far as I go.
威廉
William?
你就是在这里看见布里格斯少校的吗
Is this where you saw Major Briggs?
是的
It is.
你是怎么进去的
How did you get inside?
围栏上有个洞
The hole in the fence over there.
你往里走了多远
How far in there did you go?
大约五六米
About 15 or 20 feet.
之后发生了什么
What happened after that?
我不记得了
I don't remember what happened.
戈登
Gordon.
我看见了
I see it.
好的
Okay.
就是这里
This is the place.
他从这里进到围栏里面大约五六米
He went in through the fence here about 15 or 20 feet.
他记不起来之后发生的事了
He can't remember what happened after that.
你觉得里面有人吗  艾伯特
Think there's one in there, Albert?
很快就能揭晓了
We'll soon find out.
你掩护我们  塔米
You cover us, Tammy.
好的
Got it.
我想我们已经知道结果了
Well, I guess we found out.
没错  艾伯特
We sure did, Albert.
戈登
Gordon.
我猜是露丝·达文波特
Ruth Davenport, I presume.
看上去她胳膊上写了坐标
Looks like coordinates are written on her arm.
你拍下来了吗
You got a picture of it?
拍了
Yeah.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
该死
Fuck!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
听着  把所有后援都给我派过来
Listen, I need all available backup
梧桐街2240号
at 2240 Sycamore,
2240 Sycamore.
没有后援能处理这个
There's no backup for this.
发生什么了  麦克利
What the hell happened, Macklay?
他死了
He's dead.
双R餐厅
你想做什么  贝基
What do you want to do, Becky?
我恨他  我想离开他
I hate him. I want out.
你想离婚吗
You want a divorce?
不知道  我爱他
I don't know. I love him.
门的钱还有损坏公寓的赔偿
You're gonna have to pay for the door
得由你来出
and the damage to the apartment.
我才不付钱给她的公寓
I'm not paying for her apartment.
-贝基  -我不会付的
- Becky. - I'm not going to do it.
再说了  我一分钱也没有
I don't have any money, anyway!
亲爱的
Honey,
要不是我是警局的人
if I didn't work for the sheriff,
你现在就已经在监狱里了
you'd be in jail right now.
我借你一些钱
I'll loan you the money.
不要
Ugh, no.
我不能再拿你的钱了  母亲
I can't take any more money from you, Mom.
而且他会把你给我的钱都花光
And he spent everything you ever gave me, anyway.
我借给你
I'll loan you the money.
但你之后要把钱还我
But you gotta pay me back.
你要把这事搞定
And you gotta make this right.
我们要帮你离开那拖车
And we have to get you out of that trailer
还要远离他
and away from him.
他只是处于低谷时期
He's just going through a bad time right now.
贝基
Becky,
我一直没抓他的唯一原因
the only reason I haven't busted him is,
是希望他能为了你回头是岸
I was hoping he would come around for you.
我现在认为这是不可能的了
I don't think that's gonna happen.
可是这...这会实现的  我坚信
But it-it's gonna happen. I know it will.
他的心还是好的
He's good inside.
他每天都出去找工作
He goes out every day looking for work.
至少我认为他有这样做的
At least I thought he did.
卡尔说那拖车有点不对劲
Carl said things aren't right in that trailer.
他有打过你吗
Has he ever hit you?
不  没有
N-no, no.
他不是...这样的人
He's not... like that.
别这样
Come on.
希望你没看错人
I hope you're right.
从现在开始  如果他碰你一下
From now on, if he ever touches you
或者有任何违法犯罪的话
or breaks the law in any way,
我立马抓他
I'm gonna bring him down.
贝基
Becky,
我们都知道你已经长大了还结了婚
we know that you're a grown, married woman.
但我们是你的父母
But we're your parents.
我们爱你
And we love you.
还有...
And...
我们只是...我们不想失去你
we just-- we don't want to lose you.
你从挡风玻璃上掉下去的时候还好吗
Oh, w-when you flew off the windshield, are you okay?
我很抱歉  妈妈
I'm sorry, Mom.
-我没事  -我不是故意的
- I'm okay. - I didn't mean to do that.
-我真的是无心的  -我没事  我没事
- I really didn't. - I'm okay. I'm okay.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
你今晚跟我住一起  好吗
You're staying with me tonight, okay?
晚点见
See you later?
老地方吗
Same place?
所有人趴下  趴下
Everybody down! Get down!
特德  把灯关了
Toad, turn off the lights.
这是什么
What is this?
我的天  鲁斯
Oh, my God, Russ!
鲁斯  搞什么鬼
Russ, what the hell?
鲁斯  我的天
Russ! Oh, my God!
拉尔夫  他拿了把枪  鲁斯
Ralph--he's got a gun, Russ!
我的天  我的天啊  鲁斯
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, Russ!
是不是你把枪放车里的
Did you put a gun in this car?
去你的  你是怎么想的
Damn you! What were you thinking?
这枪放在副驾的盒子里的
It was in the front seat in a box.
我根本不知道它是枪
I didn't know it was a gun!
他可能杀了自己
He could have killed himself!
他还可能把我们都杀了
He could have killed all of us!
它就在我的脚边  鲁斯
It was by my feet, Russ.
我把它移开了不想它挡道
I moved it to get it out of the way.
你觉得我知道它是枪的话
Do you think I would have put it
会把它放在后面跟拉尔夫一起吗
in the backseat of the car with Ralph if I knew it was a gun?
你傻的吗
Are you a fucking moron?
你脑子出什么问题了
What is wrong with you?
-女士  -什么事
- Ma'am. - Yes?
我在双峰镇警察局工作
I'm with the Twin Peaks Sheriff's Department,
我是布利格斯警官
Deputy Briggs.
请把枪给我
Please hand me that gun.
好的
Okay.
给你
Here.
现在  我要你们俩的身份证
Now, I'm gonna need identification from both of you, please.
我刚刚在大艾德燃气农场
I was at Big Ed's Gas Farm.
你知道吗
And you know what?
我听到了枪声
I heard shots.
很明显  是那小孩
That kid found a gun, evidently,
在这车的后座找到了把枪
in the back of this van
然后射穿了双R餐厅的窗户
and shot through the window into the Double R.
这两位应该是他的父母
These are his parents, I think.
我要他们俩的证件
I need IDs on both of them.
女士  体谅一下
Ma'am, please!
我去叫那女人别再按喇叭
I'm gonna try and stop this woman from honking her horn
疏通一下道路
and get this traffic moving.
好的  博比
I got it, Bobby.
女士  麻烦别按了
Please, ma'am. Ma'am, please.
拜托你了  女士
Please, ma'am--
你在搞什么
What are you doing?
我们还要回家啊
We're trying to get home!
已经迟到了
We're already late.
晚餐迟到了  六点半已经过很久了
We're late for dinner. It's way past 6:30.
为什么遇到这种事
Why is this happening?
我看见那把枪朝窗外开枪
I saw that gun go shooting out the window.
她舅舅也会来
Her uncle is joining us.
她已经很久
She hasn't seen him
没有见到他了
in a very long while.
我们迟到了
We're late!
还有好几公里的路啊
We've got miles to go!
拜托  我们得回家了
Please, we have to get home!
她生病了
She's sick!
我的天
Oh, God!
双峰镇警察局
据我推算  我们要去的就是这
By my reckoning, this is where we're headed.
但那无路可走  路不通
But there's no road. The road's gone.
我一直在思考布里格斯少校所提供的信息
The information that Major Briggs gave got me thinking.
等我解释了我的地图后
You'll understand a lot more
你会更明白的
when I explain my map.
这张地图虽古老
This map is very old,
但永不过时
but it is always current.
它有生命
It's-it's a living thing.
这是布里格斯少校曾派驻的地方
This is where Major Briggs' station was.
这是蓝松山
This is Blue Pine Mountain
一个备受尊敬的的圣地
and a-a very revered sacred site.
我认为少校给我们的信息
I think that the information that the major gave us
要把我们指向那里
is gonna take us here.
这看似篝火的东西是什么
Looks like a campfire. What is this?
那不是篝火  是一个象征火的符号
It's not a campfire. It's-it's a-a fire symbol.
什么意思
What's that mean?
那是...
It's a...
一种火
a type of fire.
更类似于...
More like...
当今的电力
like modern-day electricity.
是好事吗
Good?
那要看情况  其意图为何
Depends, depends upon the intention,
火焰背后的意图是什么
the intention behind the fire.
少校也给了我们一个日期
The major also gave us a date,
也就是后天
day after tomorrow.
你观测这些星相
If you read these stars,
也能得出相同日期
you find that same date,
它会把你指向这里
and it refers you to here.
这是什么
What is this?
玉米  代表着富饶
It's corn. It's fertility.
但它是黑色的
But it's-it's black,
也就是有病害或异常的
diseased or unnatural.
死亡
Death.
若你结合这两个符号
If you put these two symbols together,
就会得到这个
you get this.
黑色火焰
Black fire.
没错
Correct.
我们在布里格斯少校的小管子里
We saw this on that little slip of paper
取出来的字条上有看见这个
we took out of Major Briggs' tube.
这是什么
What is this?
弗兰克
Frank...
你不会想知道的
you don't ever want to know about that.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
我也不知道我考虑家具做什么
I don't know why I'm even thinking about furniture.
我和安迪几乎都不在家
Andy and I hardly ever get home.
有什么事  露西
What's up, Lucy?
玛格丽特·兰特曼找您  在二线  霍克
Margaret Lanterman for you on line two, Hawk.
就是我挂电话后会闪灯的那一线
That's the one that's blinking when I hang up.
你好  玛格丽特
Hello, Margaret.
霍克
Hawk?
听得见吗
Can you hear me?
可以  玛格丽特
Yes, Margaret.
霍克  听得见吗
Hawk, can you hear me?
请说  玛格丽特
Yes, Margaret.
你是不是发现了什么
You found something, didn't you?
正如你所说的
It's just like you said.
我很抱歉  我该告诉你的
I'm sorry, I-I should have let you know.
你发现了什么  霍克
What did you find, Hawk?
玛格丽特  我不能告诉你
Margaret, I can't tell you that.
我的木头害怕火
My log is afraid of fire.
你要去的地方有火
There's fire where you are going.
霍克
Hawk,
你要去的地方有火
there's fire where you are going.
好的  玛格丽特
Okay, Margaret.
晚安  霍克
Good night, Hawk.
晚安
Good night.
谢谢你  玛格丽特
And thank you, Margaret.
什么事  杰西
What is it, Jesse?
杜鲁门警长
Sheriff Truman,
你有兴趣看我的新车吗
are you interested in seeing my new car?
-是一台20...  -杰西
- It's a two-thousand-- - Jesse.
我在开会
I'm in a meeting.
我能明天再欣赏你的新车吗
Can I look at your new car tomorrow?
好
Okay.
谢谢  杜鲁门警长
Thank you, Sh-Sheriff Truman.
坐立不安啊
Cat on a hot tin roof.
从来不会这样的
It's never done that before.
我们该来一点咖啡
We're supposed to get some coffee,
但我想这样可能不太好
but I don't think that's a good idea.
咖啡
Coffee?
我想喝咖啡啊
I would like some coffee.
或许温牛奶会好一点
Maybe some warm milk.
因为你说...
For the cat.
坐立不安
On the roof?
对
Yes.
你拍的那张露丝的照片
The picture you took of Ruth.
我想看一下  艾伯特
I would like to see it, Albert.
我能在这抽烟吗
Can I smoke in here?
抽烟
Smoke?
等麦克利回来你再问他
Ask Macklay when he gets back.
抽烟对你有害
But smoking's bad for you.
我知道
I know.
"去你的  艾伯特"
"Fuck you, Albert."
没错
That's right.
去你的  艾伯特
Fuck you, Albert.
这些坐标代表什么地方
What place do those coordinates represent?
最后几位数字糊了
Well, the last few digits are smudged,
但这些数字指向北方的一个小镇
but the numbers indicate a small town in the north--
警察的美梦成真
The policeman's dream.
谢谢  麦克利警探
Thank you, Detective Macklay.
不客气
You're welcome.
我能在这抽烟吗
Hey, can I smoke in here?
不行  这里禁烟
No, there's no smoking allowed.
麦克利警探
Detective Macklay,
你知道香烟配上这咖啡会有多美味吗
you know how good a cigarette would taste with this coffee?
你有烟就抽吧
Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以
So...
附近并无可疑人物
...no suspects were found in the area.
身份已确认是露丝·达文波特
It's a positive ID on Ruth Davenport.
我想你们应该没找到布里格斯少校的头
I don't suppose you found Major Briggs' head anywhere.
我们找了
We looked.
毫无踪迹
There's no trace.
没有人听到声音  没有枪声
Nobody heard anything. No shots.
黑斯廷斯的死状不是子弹造成的
A bullet didn't do that to Hastings.
是的  他们仍在清洗车辆
Yeah, they're still cleaning the vehicle.
我们有看到人  我和艾伯特
We saw somebody, Albert and I,
就在我们发现露丝·达文波特尸体的地方后面
out back, out back where we found Ruth Davenport's body.
他长什么样子
What'd he look like?
像个流浪汉
He looked like a homeless man, uh...
衣服破旧  留胡子  戴毛帽
old clothes, beard, wool cap.
我好像有看到那样的人
I think I saw somebody like that
离开警车
getting out of the police car.
我有可能看错了
Uh, I-I could be mistaken.
我当时在车上
Well, I was in the car.
半个人影也没看到
I-I didn't see anybody.
我也没看到任何人
I didn't see anyone either.
我都说了我不确定了
Well, I-I said I wasn't sure.
我想起来了
Now I remember.
我见过他们...
I saw them...
在一个房间里
in a room.
我见过那群留胡子的人
I saw the bearded men,
跟我和艾伯特一起见过的一样
the same type Albert and I saw.
那间屋里的那群脏兮兮的留胡子的人
Dirty, bearded men in a room.
道吉  来我办公室一趟
Dougie, come into my office, please.
穆林斯先生  我是菲尔·拜斯比
Mr. Mullins, Phil Bisby here.
咖啡已经买好了  我们马上就到
I got your coffee and we'll be right in.
好的
Good.
穆林斯先生  这杯是您的咖啡
All right, Mr. Mullins, here's your coffee, sir.
-谢谢你  菲尔  -不客气
- Thank you, Phil. - You're welcome.
坐下吧  道吉
Sit down, Dougie.
你出去的时候
Just close the door behind you
顺便把门关上  菲尔
when you go, Phil.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
道吉
Dougie,
我好好想了想这件事
now that I've had time to think about this,
你的调查结果显然已经
it's clear that your investigative work
揭露出了一系列的犯罪集团
has exposed a ring of organized crime
也有可能牵扯到这一届内部的
and possible police corruption
警察腐败问题
flowing through this office.
鉴于最近有两起企图谋杀你的案件
The recent two attempts on your life,
把你的车炸了  还有人想要射杀你
the blowing up your car, the man trying to shoot you,
这已经很说明问题了
absolutely confirm this.
还有  多亏了你  我们才能知道
Also, thanks to you, we now know that
米彻姆兄弟的案子并不是一桩纵火案
the Mitchum brothers' case was not arson
而是想从火灾中要点索赔
but a legitimate claim for an accidental fire,
所以我觉得虽然米彻姆兄弟
which indicates to me that the Mitchum brothers,
是臭名昭著的黑帮成员
although alleged gangsters,
但这起阴谋却不是他们策划的
are not part of this conspiracy,
也就说明对你的袭击的策划者
which suggests that the shots are being called
另有其人
by somebody else.
Somebody else.
你说得对  道吉
I think you're right, Dougie.
有意思的就是这点
And this is interesting.
米彻姆兄弟刚刚给我打电话
The Mitchums just called me,
说想约你当面谈一谈
wanting to have a personal sit-down with you.
一般情况下
Now, normally,
我绝对不会让我的探员
I wouldn't put one of my agents
去和那种人单打独斗
into the ring with guys like this,
可既然是你发现的
but since you uncovered
而且也替他们正了名
and righted the wrong on their behalf,
等他们拿到了你带去的
they are gonna be ecstatic
这张三千万的支票
when you deliver to them
肯定会高兴到乐上天的
this 30-million-dollar check.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
你肯定在想"这张三千万的支票
You're thinking, "A 30-million-dollar payout
我们这种小公司怎么掏得起"  对吧
for a firm our size, that has to be catastrophic," Right?
确实掏不起
Catastrophic, right.
可拳击新星
But Battling Bud
永远要打比他强的对手
always punched above his weight class.
我还备了另一套方案
I took out a secondary policy
来掩盖我们这次行动
to cover our play on this one,
因为这个案子确实是个意外
which, because it was truly was an accident,
我们就能借此补偿损失  还能再捞一笔
will cover our potential loss and then some.
布什内尔双连击
Bushnell double down.
拳击新星是不会一直被吊打的
Nobody keeps Battling Bud on the ropes for long.
最强硬汉
布什内尔·拳击新星·穆林斯
他们要五点半见你
They want to see you at 5:30.
他们会派车来
They're sending a car.
他刚从浴室里出来
He's just coming out of the bathroom now.
好吧...
All right...
罗德尼
Rodney.
我做了个梦
I had a dream.
是吗
Did ya?
一整晚都是这个梦
Had it all fuckin' night.
我梦见我要去杀那个混蛋道格拉斯·琼斯
I dreamt about killing that Douglas Jones fuck.
我实在是太恨他了
I just hate him so bad.
简直等不及想要杀了他
I can't wait to kill this guy.
你还能再等上三个小时吗
Can you last three more hours?
不一定
Barely.
我实在没胃口
I can't eat this.
道吉  已经五点半了  你要去哪
Dougie, it's 5:30. Where are you going?
你已经拿到支票了  不是吗
You've got the check, don't you?
是的  你都准备好了
Yeah, you're all set.
你要带他去哪里
Where you taking him?
圣蒂诺
Santino's.
你会喜欢那里的
Oh, you're gonna like that.
我等你好消息  冠军
I'm in your corner, champ.
把他们干死
Knock 'em dead.
死
Dead.
红色的门
Red door.
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么了  布拉德利
What is with you, Bradley?
开心点
Be happy.
我们马上就要干掉一个
We're about to rid ourselves of an asshole
给我们捅了大大大篓子的家伙
who has majorly, majorly fucked us over.
他帮我们干掉了艾克穗
Well, he nailed Ike the Spike for us.
他不是为了我们
He didn't do that for us.
再说  他让我们损失了三千万
Plus, he lost our 30 million, and then
他卷走我们赌场472000元
he takes our casino for 472 grand.
没错  你说得对  我知道
Yeah, yeah, you're right. I know. You're right.
我当然没错
You're damn right I'm right.
我知道
I know.
怎么了
What?
我的梦
My dream.
又要说你的梦
Ah, the dream again.
在梦里
In the dream--
In the dream,
坎迪给你留下的伤痕完全痊愈了
your Candie cut was completely healed.
什么
What?
坎迪划伤你的伤痕
The cut Candie gave you.
怎么可能
How can that be?
-过来  -不  不  别
- Come here. - No, no, stop.
-布拉德利  住手  -过来  别动
- Bradley, stop it. - Come here. Hold still.
-你干什么  -放松
- What are you doing? - Easy.
别动  这很...
Stop it. It's gonna-- -
天啊
I'll be damned.
怎么...
How--
没错
Yeah.
还有呢
There's more.
但我记不起来了
But I can't remember.
待会见  艾尔
See ya later, Al.
不  等等
No, wait, wait.
稍等一下
Hold on a minute.
怎么了
What?
-怎么了  -过来
- What? - Come here.
过来
Come around here.
你看到他拿的那个箱子了吗
You see that box that he's holding there?
怎么了
Yeah?
我梦里也有
That was in my dream.
-操  -不
- Ah, fuck. - No.
听我说  听我说
Listen to me. Listen to me.
那盒子里有东西
There's something in that box.
如果这是我在梦里看到的东西
And if that something is what I saw in my dream,
我们就不能杀他
we can't kill him.
你他妈在说...
What the fuck are you talking--
不  我没开玩笑  罗德尼
No, I'm not kidding, Rodney.
如果他箱子里装的
If he's got this one certain thing
是那个东西
that's in that box,
那说明我们不能杀他
it means we can't kill him.
为什么
Why?
那说明他不是我们的敌人  罗德尼
It means he's not our enemy, Rodney.
你怎么知道
How the fuck can you know that?
我就是告诉你梦里的东西
I-I'm just telling you what was in the dream.
但肯定有一件事是确定的
But it's gotta be this one certain thing.
什么
What?
罗德尼  虽然机会不大
Rodney, it's a million-in-one shot,
但如果的确在里面  你得...
but if it's in there, you got--
你得向我保证
you gotta promise me.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们要一起面对
We gotta be together on this.
好
Okay.
我们不杀他
We won't kill him.
够了  到底是什么
Okay, enough. What is it?
好吧
All right.
搞什么
Okay. What the fuck?
盒子里
In the box there,
是个樱桃派吗
is that a cherry pie?
樱桃派
Cherry pie.
Cherry pie!
以防万一  搜他身
Frisk him just in case.
连钱包都没有
Doesn't even have a wallet.
这是给我们的
It's addressed to us.
打开
Open it.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我的...
Holy...
我爱这家伙
I love this guy!
道吉
Dougie?
道吉·琼斯
Dougie Jones.
-很高兴见到你  -很高兴认识你
- What a pleasure to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
你是说你孩子没有
You mean to say your kid doesn't have one?
没有健身房
No gym set?
No gym set.
天
Jeez.
连我们该死的孤儿都有健身房
Even our fucking orphanage had a gym set.
每个孩子都应该有个健身房
Every kid should have a gym set.
给  哥们
There you go, brother.
好
Yeah.
祝酒
A toast.
道吉
Dougie.
敬你的  道吉
Here's to you, Dougie.
大奖先生
Mr. Jackpots!
这就是我跟你说得那个人
This is the man I told you about.
我一直想再见你
I wanted to see you again.
我每天都在想你
I've thought of you every day,
想你为我做的事
what you did for me.
你改变了我的人生
You changed my life.
这是我的乖儿子  丹佛
This is my dear son, Denver.
他又回到我身边了
He's back in my life again.
我养了一条小狗
I have a little dog.
我有了一个房子
I have a house.
我的人生都回来了
I have my life back again.
我该怎么谢谢你
How can I ever thank you?
希望你们知道和你们共进晚餐的人
I hope you realize what a special person
有多么特别
you having dining with you.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
也救了我们很多
Sure saved us a lot too.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你  大奖先生
Thank you, Mr. Jackpots.
我太高兴了
I'm so thankful I got
能有机会再向你道谢
a chance to say thank you again.
再向你道谢
Thank you again.
上来了
Here it is.
终于
Finally.
还有姑娘们
And here are the girls.
坎迪
Candie.
Candie?
坎迪  看着我
Candie, look at me.
你都去哪儿了
Where have you been?
坎迪
Candie.
路上有好多车
There was so much traffic on the Strip.
太厉害了
It was incredible.
到处都是车
There were cars everywhere.
这个派太好吃了
This pie is so damn good.
太好吃
Damn good.
祝酒
A toast.
道吉
Dougie.
敬救了你一命的派  道吉
Here's to the pie that saved your life, Dougie.
和钱
And our money.
坎迪
Candie.
再给我们的朋友来一块派
Another piece of pie for our friend.
朋友
Friend.